Hollow Point is a action, comedy, thriller film directed by Sidney J. Furie.
Livingston is trying to merge the Russians, Chinese and Italian
gangsters into one group with huge amounts of money and power.
FBI agent Susan and DEA agent Max are trying to stop them.
Garrett Lawton, played by Donald Sutherland.
Thomas Livingston, played by John Lithgow.
Diane Norwood, played by Tia Carrere.
Max Parrish, played by Thomas Ian Griffith.
Oleg Krezinsky, played by David Hemblen.
Alberto Capucci, played by Carl Alacchi.
Hollow Point is a 1996 film directed by Sidney J.
Furie and starring Thomas Ian Griffith, Tia Carrere,
John Lithgow, and Donald Sutherland.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.